export const data = [
  {
    question: "I lost my login email adress, what should I do ? ",
    answer:
      "If you forget/lose your login email address, we invite you to contact us via our contact form or social networks. We will do our best to help you find it. Do not hesitate to provide your full name that may be associated with your account.",
  },
  {
    question: "Where can I find my subscription or credit bills ",
    answer:
      "Your invoices and all payments for video content made on our website (full subscription; credit to view our masterclasses / videos) can be downloaded in your account.",
  },
  {
    question: "I have a problem with my subsciption, my credits, my payment, what should I do?",
    answer:
      "For any problem related to subscriptions, credits and payments, we invite you to contact us via our contact form or social networks, we will try our best to help you find it. Do not hesitate to give us your name, first name and email address associated with your account so that we can find you more easily.",
  },
  {
    question: "How does the subsciption work?",
    answer:
      "Our subscription of €29.90 per month (special offer at €9.90 per month) gives you unlimited access to all our masterclasses and videos. Your subscription is automatically renewed from one month to the next. If you wish to terminate your subscription, you can do so on your account page.",
  },
  {
    question: "The masterclass or the video is not displayed, what should I do",
    answer:
      "If the masterclass you want to watch does not appear, check your Wi-Fi connection. Verify that your connection is good and that you are indeed subscribed or have rented the video. If you have done all the above and you are still experiencing difficulty with viewing the video, please contact us via our contact form or social media networks and we will happily find a solution to your problem.",
  },

  {
    question: "How does video on demand work? ",
    answer:
    " Our video on demand offer allows you to rent the videos of your choice for a period of 3 months.",
 },
 {
  question: "who are the teachers in our academy? ",
  answer:
  " The teachers of our masterclasses are all internationally renowned musicians, first prize winners, judges of major musical competitions and recognized professors. Each of them has a pedagogical experience, which is intended to transmit to the academicians their knowledge, acquired over the years.",
},
{
  question: " Can I apply for a scholarship? ",
  answer:
  " Yes, you must apply when you fill out the application form. If your application is accepted, you will be eligible to receive a scholarship of at least €100 and up to 450€.",
},
{
  question: "can minors register?",
  answer:
  " Yes, they must be accompanied by a responsible parent or legal guardian. If not, the signature of one or the other is required and a statement releasing the Saline royale Academy from all responsibility must be provided upon final registration of the student.",
},
{
  question: "Where and when can I watch my recorded lessons? ",
  answer:
  "The recorded lessons are published on the Saline royale Academy platform several months after the academy: they need post-production, subtitles, and we follow a strict calendar to make sure we alternate publications between instruments. When your videos are online, we create a free access for you to watch them.",
}
,

];
export const professeurs = [
  { titleProf: "Silvia Careddu", textProf: "Distinguée par plusieurs prix internationaux, a étudié la flûte à Cagliari et à Paris. Sa carrière s'est épanouie en 2002 avec la Filarmonica Arturo Toscanini, et elle a collaboré avec des orchestres renommés en Europe. En plus d'être membre fondatrice du Alban Berg Ensemble Wien, elle enseigne la flûte dans diverses institutions et participe fréquemment à des jurys de concours internationaux.", imageProf: "" },
  { titleProf: "Ning Feng", textProf: "Est un violoniste renommé pour son grand lyrisme et sa virtuosité. Acclamé internationalement, il a collaboré avec des orchestres majeurs tels que le Hong Kong Philharmonic et le Royal Liverpool Philharmonic Orchestra. En Chine, il est particulièrement estimé et a été artiste résident de l'Orchestre symphonique de Shanghai. Ses enregistrements, y compris son disque récent ", imageProf: "" },
  { titleProf: "Mary Brennan", textProf: "Diplômée du Royal Northern College of Music, a enseigné au DIT Conservatory et au Royal Northern College of Music. Depuis 2007, elle enseigne à la Royal Irish Academy of Music, spécialisée dans les études vocales et la chanson française. Plusieurs de ses étudiants ont réussi, et certains ont remporté la prestigieuse bourse Royal Dublin Society", imageProf: "" },
];